

## **OBJECTIVES**

I work to develop myself in various fields and I like to learn new things I have experiences and adventures to learn and gain experience, I have professional photography skills and I have many awards and achievements in this field.

In addition to being a member of the Bahrain Photographic Society, I have also participated in photography exhibitions and conferences and do special sessions in the art of photographic processing.



Photo Galleries: Families ▶ Weddings ▶ Business Portraits ▶ peoples life ▶ Sports ▶ Events



## PERSONAL DETILS

Hassan Dawood Jassem Dawood



• hassanbindawood@gmail.com



• House: 2469, Road: 3779, Block: 1037 Sadad Village.



● 08/February/1991



+973 33907352 - 37736695

Bahraini



## **SKILLS**

Photography skills • Airtight in some photography competitions

Portrait photography and Editing

Computer

Adobe Photoshop

MS Office Skills

**Ohers Skills** 

- Adaptability
- Self-motivation
- solve technical problems quickly

- Private lessons in photography and Photoshop
- Basic skills in videography
- Adobe Lightroom
- Communication skills
- Creative thinking skills



## **ACTIVITIES**



Photography



Gym



Movies



Football



Music



## **LANGUGES**

Reading and Writing

Arabic Fluent **English** Good

Speaking

Fluent Good



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Machine Operator | Medal Cable Company

SAUDI ARABIA BRANCH: 2014 - 2017 / BAHRAIN BRANCH: 2017 - CURRENT

I worked in the Saudi Arabia branch in advance and then I was transferred to the Bahrain branch, My Task:

- Operating cables making machines and following up their work.
- Repair any cable interruptions and welding cables.

## Worker | Hassan and Habib Sons Mahmood Company

2011 - 2012

Worked in the company as a worker to transport foods from warehouses to customers such as: restaurants, hotels and supermarkets



## **EDUCATION**

## High School Certificate | Al-Jabriya Industrial School

2009 - 2011

Vocational training certificate



# **PHOTOGRAPHY AWARDS**

Arab Photographers Award | Bahrain

2018

Oman International Competition | Oman

2017

Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum Competition | Dubai

2016

Many awards | Serbia, Croatia and many other countries

2016 - 2019